## S.Arockia Naveen

#### **B.E-CSE**

Full Stack Web Developer (MERN Stack) & React Native

+918778615921 naveen1337@outlook.com

Pudukkottai

Tamil Nadu - 622303

naveen1337.github.io github.com/naveen1337 linkedin.com/in/naveen1337/

#### **About**

Undergraduate Computer Science Engineer.

Full-Stack web developer Expertise in React.js, NodeJS, Postgres, Fastify with 3 Year Experience

Cross platform mobile application developer using **React Native** Framework

Expertise in Linux, Nginx and Cloud Environment, and Enthusiastic in Data science with Python

## **Experience**

## 1. React Native Developer

Gtech Web Solutions-Pudukkottai

From 11/2020 to 4/2022

Food Delivery Application, has a feature of Multi Store products, Order Placement, Live Tracking, Pick and drop and Push Notifications, Clean UI With tailwind CSS,

## 2. React Js/ React Native Developer

Sabbatech Solution - Chennai

From 04 / 2022 to Present

Developed a Field survey collection application for US with admin panel and react native app, that includes volunteer flow and census block map Integration

## **Projects**

## 1. Food Delivery Application (React Native) 04 / 2021

Food Delivery Application, has a feature of Multi Store products, Order Placement, Live Tracking, Pick and drop and Push Notifications, Clean UI With tailwind CSS,

Technologies: Javascript, React Native, Redux, REST API

#### **Skills**

- 1. Javascript & Typescript
- 2. React.js & React Native
- 3. Redux, Reselect
- 4. Node.js & Express.js
- 5. Postgresql
- 6. MySQL & MongoDB
- 7. Python & Data Science
- 8. AWS & Linux

## **Languages**

- 1. Tamil (Native)
- English (Professional Level)

#### Soft Skills

- 1. Self Taught
- 2. Reverse Engineering

#### **Interests**

- 1. Data Science
- 2. Progressive Web Apps
- 3. Machine Learning
- 4. Cyber Security
- 5. Block Chain

## 2. Distribution system with Field Survey (Nodejs, React.js, React Native)

07/2022

Book distribution and field survey application in US with census block map and volunteers flow, Worked on a Admin panel in React.js and Mobile application with React Native

Technologies: Node.js, React.js, React Native, ArcGIS Maps

## 3. Recommender System (Python)

12/2020

Scalable Recommender system build on Psychographics (OCEAN) Modal, used to recommended items by analyzing user attributes. (College Final Year Project)

Technologies: Python, Pandas, Scikit learn, Numpy

## **Education**

### **B.E / Computer Science (**CGPA: 6.5)

Mount Zion College of Engineering and Technology

08/2016 - 05/2020

Thirumayam, Pudukkottai

## **Higher Secondary (75%)**

St. Joseph's Higher Secondary School

06/2014 - 04/2016

Venkatakulam, Pudukkottai

#### **Achievements**

### The Onion Router & Journalist Freedom

Parisutham Institute of Technology and Science - Thanjavur

08/2018

Paper Presentation - Third Place

## **Browser Fingerprinting based Tracking**

Mookambigai College of Engineering - Pudukkottai

09/2018

Paper Presentation - Second Place

### **DDOS Threats & Mitigation Strategies**

Chendhuran College of Engineering and technology - Pudukkottai

02/2019

Paper Presentation - Second Place

#### **Online Courses**

## CentOS Enterprise Linux 7 Operation Essentials

04/2020

By Andrew Mallett from

Pluralsight.

# Security Enhanced Linux (SELinux) Fundamentals

04/2020

By Nigel Poulton from Pluralsight

Web Application Penetration Testing with Burp Suite

04/2020

By Dr.Sunny Wear from

Pluralsight